All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Horty Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict and find themselves in the midst of an all-out war.
Now, it's time to set up the fireworks!
Cut. Sauric party's over.
Quinto tieris.
Fantasia.
Mille Blue.
Gigantesco Mono.
And stop!
Soldier Duck System.
Channel Four.
It's F.R.U.
Fall.
Just leave it to me, boys.
Ah!
The new number!
Channel Five!
Racheotank Five is here!
Ah!
Ooh!
Losero!
Ah!
Thank you very much for lending us your power, Tsutamae.
Iron Pirate, here comes General Frankie.
They've got a lot of nerve.
But hey, so do I!
Kiki!
Hey, where the hell am I?
Conchcord Plaza, have you forgotten already?
Hmm?
Uh...
Well, if the swords weren't that good, this ought to be interesting, eh?
Everyone out of my way!
No! Run, you're done!
Run away! Hurry!
Come on! Really?
I was having fun, but now they're all too chicken to fight!
Well, I don't blame them. I am pretty awesome.
Might as well knock out their officers while they're gone, right?
Woo! Onward!
I can see the ugly red one at 12 o'clock!
Play game!
Roger! Preparing to fire!
Huh? Where did he go?
Cookie cutter!
He's over there! Fire!
Got you this time! Not again!
He's right over there! Get him!
Gah! Are you kidding me?!
No, he's not there!
Can't hit him! That little creep is way too quick!
Hey! Come in, Commander Chopper!
I'm guessing it's not supposed to be shaking like that, right? What's up?
A-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a!
It serves you right! I call that one the Daruma Drop!
Ow!
Kya-kya!
While you morons were shooting at nothing, I dug a whole maze of tunnels under this place!
Huh?
Hey!
Where'd you go?
Usa!
Chopper!
Perfect! Now all I have to do is trick their biker buddy into...
What the hell?! Who put a sinkhole here?!
What?! How stupid are you?!
That hurt.
Yeah, you're telling me. That was a pretty big drop.
You just made a super mistake, Short Stuff!
Everybody off the tank! Get it!
What are you?!
Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah!
Not getting along?
Geez, Frankie, why did you throw us out like that?
Have some respect for your commander, pal!
Sorry, but the next form has only got one seat!
Let's get freaky!
You're freaky enough already!
Black Rhino, FRU-4!
Oh!
Stand back!
Whoa! Super Freaky!
Hold your applause!
Brachio tank bye!
Racheotank 5!
Headshames!
Black Rhino F.R.U. 4!
Docking phase!
Whoa! So fancy!
Meet the Iron Pirate!
General Ranking!
Whoa!
This is crazy!
No way!
We'd rather get a giant fighting robot!
This is a dream come true!
Whoa!
Ha ha ha!
I still haven't met the mad genius Vegapunk!
But I finally made his dream come true!
Even if it did take a whole two years of trial and error!
By manipulating the shaped memory alloy known as waffle metal!
I've built a big ass robot!
Come on, man!
It's just a bucket of bolts!
Yeah!
Ah!
I've built a big ass robot!
Come on, man!
It's just a bucket of bolts!
He's got a bucket of bolts!
Whoa! Look at him go!
Oh, I'm just getting started, bro!
This baby's called the plunderer's sword!
Franken!
A sword cannon!
General!
Watch your step!
He's swinging low!
You winds can jump up and down all you want,
but I'll blast you straight out of the sky!
Whee! I want shoulder cannons!
Frankie Cannon!
Not what I was expecting!
But hey!
Hey!
It's still cool though!
I love this game!
Woohoo!
Ha ha!
Yeah!
Ho ho ho!
Ha ha ha!
Ah!
Damn this guy!
What now?
Ha! Don't worry!
There's plenty more where that came from!
Woo! Stay away!
Yes!
I'm fine!
General!
Wait!
That's right Frankie!
General!
Wait!
That's right Frankie!
General!
Looks lame to me.
Hey!
You must be one of the weaker ones, huh?
Duh!
Who says I'm weak?
I just like it when other people do all the work!
Sorcery Climb Attacked!
This one is gonna blow you away!
Time for the Gustsword!
I learned that back in with Aria.
That's hardcore meteorology!
Now who's weak?
Wait a sec!
Where's Chopper?
Come on!
Let's get that guy over there!
Oh man!
Guess I'm officially off the tank now!
Guess I gotta fight by myself!
You don't scare me!
I'm not some little weenie like I was before!
Special Attack!
Green Style!
Bamboo Javelin!
I hope you're proud Master!
I'll never forget those two crazy years I spent training with you in the Swindling Forest!
This is the next chapter of life!
The legend of the great hero Usopp is beginning right here and now!
I'm gonna dig sinkholes all over this plaza!
It doesn't matter how powerful that ridiculous robot is if he drives it into a hole then it's all over!
What's that noise?
That can't be right!
Sounds like someone else is here!
Huh?
Huh?!
He shot straight out of the ground!
Huh?
Who are you?
Look close!
Huh?
I can dig holes, too!
My horn point really came in handy, huh?
That's cool!
Wow!
You can turn into a big hairy bug and you never told me?
Oh, that is so rude!
You should know.
I spent the last two years working on all seven of my transformation points.
Now I'm so good that I only need the rumble ball for one of them.
So I can use all my other forms whenever I want to.
You coral head pain in the ass!
I'm so gonna bite you!
They're not coral, they're horns like a monster.
And you are about to see what this monster can do!
Those straw hats are crazy!
Looks like they're having a blast out there!
If I had powers like that, I'd want to let loose on those jerks, too!
How many have we killed?
Not a single one.
I don't know what you did to gain Straw Hat's trust, but that doesn't matter.
You might salvage this yet.
You've got the princess where I want her.
Now squeeze the life out of her, will you?
Did you perhaps forget your brother at the North Pole?
I know exactly where he is right now.
My men and I can go there and slaughter him anytime we please.
I wouldn't mind killing you or your family.
The corpses of mythical beasts are quite valuable.
But that won't be a problem because you're on my side, right?
It's your choice.
What?
So the Kraken agreed to do Hordy's breeding to ensure the safety of his brother?
This is your last chance.
I said squeeze that mermaid to death now!
Please, Sudirme!
Stop it!
You're hurting me!
You wanted to save your brother's life, so you did whatever this jerk told you?
I know what that's like.
So, is he your big brother?
Or your little brother?
If you need someone to save him, then count on me!
Just ask next time.
After all, we're friends, right?
Oh, thank you, Sudirme!
It's coming this way!
Let's get him!
Hurray!
You're no match for our leader!
Leave this one to me here!
We won't let you get one step closer to our captain!
Back off!
You go through me first!
We have to stop Straw Hat!
All right, second gear!
Hey, where'd he go?
What the-
That's enough!
I'm done with you!
Awesome!
I didn't even see him move!
That was crazy!
Yeah!
What the hell?
It's coming!
Yeah!
Awesome!
I didn't even see him move!
That was crazy!
It can't be.
That's the Ship of Promise, NOAH.
As the battle between Luffy and Hordy rages on, a foreboding shadow is cast upon Concord Plaza.
The citizens stare on in terror as the great ship NOAH hurtles towards the island.
Shirohoshi stands in its way to protect her people, but even the massive mermaid is dwarfed by the size of the giant vessel.
On the next, One Piece, the NOAH closing in, the Fishman Island facing destruction.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!